hey guys so we have the absolute value
of 4 - 3x is equal to X absolute value
means that whatever is inside here you
need to make it positive so there are
two ways this can be true if this stuff
inside of here is equal to X or if it's
equal tox and that's usually the way you
solve these you split it up one where
you're doing the positive of this thing
and one where you're doing the negative
of this thing and now we can just solve
each of these independently let's add 3x
to both sides so on the left hand side
we just have four and on the right hand
side we have x + 3x which is 4X and
after we divide both sides by four we
get 1 is equal to X and on the other
side we can add 3x to both sides once
again the left hand side is 4 but on the
right hand side x + 3x is 2X and after
we divide both sides by two we get X is
equal to 2 and now we just got to check
our answers so for the first one let's
plug in one and for the second one let's
plug in two inside this absolute value
we have 4 Min - 3 which is equal to one
the absolute value of one is one so that
checks out and then inside of this
absolute value we have 4 - 6 which is -2
and the absolute value of -2 is 2 so
that checks out so these are the answers
to this question x = 1 or x = 2 let's
put a box around them how exciting and
if you guys want to try more of these I
have this page on andy.com the link is
in the description